Resume

Name: Jinwei Hu

Education: Bachelor of Management in Real Estate and Business English

Date of Birth: Oct 14th 1984

Language: Madarin Chinese and English

Phone: 628-233-6666

Email: jinwei1014@gmail.com

Address: 2616 Admiral Cir Hayward CA 94545

With 15 years of work experience in the IT support specialist and system integration fields, I am skilled and knowledgeable in IT problem diagnostics and solving, as well as system integration including designing, maintaining and installing. I am also familiar with windows, macOS and linux systems, network projects, servers, switches and storages, using all different kinds of tools to find and solve the problems.

Certificate (enclosed in the end):

Google IT Support Professional Certificate
California C7 Low Voltage Contractor Certificate

Position:

Network management, server room management and other related positions.

Education:

1999-2003 Jiaxing University

Major: Real Estate Management and Business English

1997-1999 Xinmi Shiyan High School

Work Experience:

2004-2006 Xinshun Shipyard Co., Ltd in Wenzhou Zhejiang

Working as an English translator and the office IT support specialist to help employees and ship owners with their IT and computer needs.

2008-2009 Nigeria Rebecca Trading Co.

Working in cooperation with my director to build and computerize a supply network system in Lagos, Nigeria.

2010-2013 China Merchants Bank in Wenzhou Zhejiang

Managing and maintaining the servers and all the other assets in the IDC center. Main job responsibility included the server diagnostics and problem solving, new server setup, wiring, hardware replacements including hard drive, storage RAM etc.

2016-2020 SF Pinnacle Limousine Inc.

Starting as a limo driver, after one year, I was promoted to work in the office to help all the dispatches and drivers with their IT needs, including building up the office internet working environment, fixing internet related problems, customizing employees' working computers and making sure they can use the hardware and software easily and efficiently.

2017 until present

Working part time in the server room, installing the servers and wiring, changing the hard drives and other hardware.

C7

License # 1063958

